Register of the Richard V. Allen papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and writings, 1961-1999 (Box-folder 62-73)
  - Book review of Kirkpatrick's Strategy of Deception, 1964 (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Articles for the National Review, 1964 (Box-folder 63: 2)
  - Speech at Ferrum Junior College, 1964 October (Box-folder 63: 3)
  - Peaceful Coexistence: draft, 1964. Includes photographs (Box-folder 63: 4)
  - Peaceful Coexistence: provisional draft, 1964 (Box-folder 63: 5)
  - Peaceful Coexistence: publicity, 1964 (Box-folder 63: 6-7)
  - Speeches and appearances, 1965 (Box-folder 63: 8)
  - Speech to the American Bar Association in Chicago, 1966 February (Box-folder 63: 9)
  - Articles: Neue Komintern and Aussenpolitik, 1966 March (Box-folder 63: 10)
  - Speech: Young Americans for Freedom, 1966 July (Box-folder 63: 11)
  - Coexistence for What? Washington Post, 1966 August 23 (Box-folder 63: 12)
  - Peaceful Coexistence: draft, 1966 (Box-folder 63: 13-14)
  - Peaceful Coexistence: draft, 1966 (Box-folder 64: 1)
  - Peaceful Coexistence: publicity, 1966 (Box-folder 64: 2-3)
  - Peaceful Coexistence: representative publicity for 1964 edition, 1966 May (Box-folder 64: 4)
  - Détente, 1967 (Box-folder 64: 5)
  - Democracy and communism correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 64: 6)
  - Essay on winning the Cold War, 1967 (Box-folder 64: 7)
  - Chapter for The New Russia, 1967 (Box-folder 64: 8)
  - Presentation: Airlie House conference, 1967 January (Box-folder 64: 9)
  - Consular Treaty, 1967 February (Box-folder 64: 10)
  - Speech to the California Republican Assembly, 1967 April 6 (Box-folder 64: 11)
  - Lecture at Westminster College, 1967 July 17 (Box-folder 64: 12)
  - ABA Television lecture, 1967 July 24 (Box-folder 64: 13)
  - Speech at San Diego State College, 1967 August 21 (Box-folder 64: 14)
  - Speech: Young Americans for Freedom, 1967 September 1 (Box-folder 64: 15)
  - Speech at West Valley Republican Women, 1967 September 28 (Box-folder 64: 16)
  - KQED TV panel discussion, 1967 September 28 (Box-folder 64: 17)
  - Commentary at Hoover Conference, 1967 October 13 (Box-folder 65: 1)
  - Debate, Vietnam Forum, 1967 October 18 (Box-folder 65: 2)
  - Debate on Proposition P, 1967 October 27 (Box-folder 65: 3)
  - Speech: Young Americans for Freedom, 1967 November (Box-folder 65: 4)
  - Speech at Lubbock Christian College, 1967 January 5 (Box-folder 65: 5)
  - ISI Seminar speech, 1967 December 28 (Box-folder 65: 6)
  - Southern California Stanford conference, 1968 February 11 (Box-folder 65: 7)
  - Far East trip, 1968 February (Box-folder 65: 8)
  - Stanford Daily, 1968 February (Box-folder 65: 9)
  - Billings, MT speech, 1968 March 21 (Box-folder 65: 10)
  - ISI Seminar on East-West trade, 1968 March 22 (Box-folder 65: 11)
  - Commonwealth Club speech, 1968 April 26 (Box-folder 65: 12)
  - Story on Korea, 1968 August 30 (Box-folder 65: 13)
  - Reviews of Yearbook on International Communist Affairs 1968, 1971 April (Box-folder 65: 14)
  - Speech at Bowling Green, 1975 October 25 (Box-folder 65: 15)
  - Sunday Observer interview, 1977 April 10 (Box-folder 65: 16)
  - Carter's Nuclear Policy: What Does it Mean for Japan?, 1977 June 30 (Box-folder 65: 17)
  - Is War Inevitable in the 1980s?, 1979 June 7 (Box-folder 65: 18)
  - Karl-Arnold Stiftung speech, 1979 November 13 (Box-folder 65: 19)
  - Sons of the Revolution speech, 1981 February 20 (Box-folder 65: 20)
  - Asahi Shimbun Interview, 1981 March 8 (Box-folder 65: 21)
  - 20/20 Interview, 1981 March 20 (Box-folder 65: 22)
  - Conservative Political Action Conference speech, 1981 March 21 (Box-folder 65: 23-24)
  - 20/20 Interview, 1981 April 2 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Reaction to 20/20 Interview, 1981 March-April (Box-folder 66: 2)
  - Peter Merseberger interview, 1981 April 29 (Box-folder 66: 3)
  - Business Council at the Homestead speech, 1981 May 9 (Box-folder 66: 4)
  - Welt am Sonntag interview, 1981 May 10 (Box-folder 66: 5)
  - CNN Interview, 1981 May 17 (Box-folder 66: 6)
  - Hanover College commencement, 1981 May. Includes photographs (Box-folder 66: 7)
  - Remarks for Solidarity Day rally for Soviet Jewry, 1981 May 31. Includes photographs (Box-folder 66: 8)
  - Nihon Keizei symposium, 1981 June 12 (Box-folder 66: 9)
  - Interview with Business Week, 1981 June 29 (Box-folder 66: 10)
  - Good Morning America interview, 1981 July 20 (Box-folder 66: 11)
  - Die Welt interview and statement, 1981 September (Box-folder 66: 12)
  - Die Zeit interview, 1981 September 10 (Box-folder 66: 13)
  - Air Force association, 1981 September 14 (Box-folder 66: 14)
  - NASA Awards Ceremony, 1981 September 15 (Box-folder 66: 15)
  - The Case for AWACS, 1981 September 20 (Box-folder 66: 16)
  - Weizman Institute dinner, 1981 September 20 (Box-folder 66: 17)
  - The Atlantic Alliance at a Crossroad, Strategic Review, 1981 Fall (Box-folder 66: 18)
  - Haifa University speech, 1981 November 4 (Box-folder 67: 1)
  - Meet the Press, 1981 November 29 (Box-folder 67: 2)
  - Richard Allen states his case on Nightline, 1981 November 30 (Box-folder 67: 3)
  - Arms buildup, Atlanta Journal and Constitution, 1982 May 23 (Box-folder 67: 4)
  - Northern Virginia Sun, 1982 June 12 (Box-folder 67: 5)
  - Response to questions posed by the National Journal, 1982 July (Box-folder 67: 6)
  - Remarks at 51st Couchiching conference, 1982 July 28 (Box-folder 67: 7)
  - German speeches file, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 67: 8)
  - Bibliography, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 67: 9-12)
  - Bibliography, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 68: 1-4)
  - USSR speech background file, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 68: 5)
  - Filbinger conference, 1983 March 12 (Box-folder 68: 6)
  - South China Morning Post, 1983 May 21 (Box-folder 68: 7)
  - Owens-Illinois Asian Advisory Council, 1983 October 21 (Box-folder 68: 8)
  - Jaycees World Congress, 1983 November 6-12 (Box-folder 68: 9)
  - American Institute for the Weitzmann Institute of Science, 1983 November 17 (Box-folder 68: 10)
  - Reagan administation and security speech background file, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 68: 11)
  - General speech file, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 68: 12)
  - Speech, pre-election, 1984 (Box-folder 68: 13)
  - Secretary's Open Forum, 1984 January 25 (Box-folder 69: 1)
  - USA Today, "Control the media to end their abuses,", 1984 April 15 (Box-folder 69: 2)
  - U.S. Policy toward Taiwan, 1984 April 30 (Box-folder 69: 3)
  - American Bar Association conference, 1984 May 11 (Box-folder 69: 4)
  - Focus Canada Forum, 1984 May 14-15 (Box-folder 69: 5)
  - Student legal forum at the University of Virginia, 1984 Spring (Box-folder 69: 6)
  - Panel discussion on Advanced Strategic Defense, 1984 July 10 (Box-folder 69: 7)
  - Hanns-Seidel-Stiftung, Fifth International Symposium on Policy and Strategy, 1984 November 8 (Box-folder 69: 8)
  - Defense and Deficit speech background file, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 69: 9)
  - Control the Media, includes an article by Chuck Lane of the New Republic, 1985 January (Box-folder 69: 10)
  - Drexel, Burnham, Lambert Conference, 1985 March (Box-folder 69: 11)
  - Korea Shin Mun article regarding Chun visit, 1985 May (Box-folder 69: 12)
  - Insight Magazine on trade war, 1985 September 23 (Box-folder 69: 13)
  - Heritage Summit briefing book, 1985 November (Box-folder 69: 14)
  - China seminar, 1986 January 28 (Box-folder 69: 15)
  - Proposal for free trade with Asia, 1986 February 24 (Box-folder 69: 16)
  - Christlich-Soziale Union speech, 1986 June 20 (Box-folder 69: 17)
  - Taiwan speech, 1986 July 8 (Box-folder 69: 18)
  - "Who should succeed Reagan?" Policy Review, 1986 Summer (Box-folder 69: 19)
  - Speech to Daimler-Benz A.G., 1986 October 31 (Box-folder 69: 20)
  - Nichols/Tufts oral history, 1987 January 19 (Box-folder 69: 21)
  - Taiwan, 1987 April 26 (Box-folder 70: 1)
  - Address to symposium on Republic of Korea - emerging industrial power, 1987 May 8 (Box-folder 70: 2)
  - American leadership conference, 1987 May 23 (Box-folder 70: 3)
  - Free Trade Conference, 1987 June 17 (Box-folder 70: 4)
  - Die Reagan-Revolution: Ihr Anspruch, Ihr Ende, 1987 (Box-folder 70: 5)
  - George Bush, Northern Virginia Sun, 1988 May 7 (Box-folder 70: 6)
  - "Trading with Tigers," Asian Wall Street Journal, 1988 September 16 (Box-folder 70: 7)
  - Hanns-Seidel-Stiftung, 1988 November 13 (Box-folder 70: 8)
  - "The Pacific Basin", Thinking About America: The United States in the 1990s, 1988 (Box-folder 70: 9)
  - The 1988 U.S. Elections, undated (Box-folder 70: 10)
  - Georgetown University speech, 1989 April 19 (Box-folder 70: 11)
  - Interview with Lou Cannon, 1989 April 27 (Box-folder 70: 12)
  - Cultural capital, 1989 May 16 (Box-folder 70: 13)
  - Great Decisions reception, Foreign Policy Association, 1989 June 19 (Box-folder 70: 14)
  - Dossier magazine, 1989 July (Box-folder 70: 15)
  - U.S. - Republic of Korea relationship, 1989 October 10 (Box-folder 70: 16)
  - American Interests panel with Morton Kondracke, 1989 October 13 (Box-folder 70: 17)
  - Asian Real Estate Association, 1989 November 1 (Box-folder 70: 18)
  - Regardie's magazine article on Crédit Internationale Bank, 1990 January (Box-folder 70: 19)
  - Speeches and Writings, 1961-1999 (cont.) (Box-folder 70)
  - Lunch speech to McDonnell D., 1990 January 30 (Box-folder 70: 20)
  - Interview in Free China Journal, 1990 May 31 (Box-folder 70: 21)
  - Speech at Amerika Haus, Munich, 1990 June (Box-folder 70: 22)
  - "The Gulf," Crossfire, 1991 January 8 (Box-folder 70: 23)
  - Hypotheticals TV panel on the Gulf, 1991 June (Box-folder 70: 24)
  - Adenauer piece for Policy Review, 1991 November 19 (Box-folder 70: 25)
  - ASC lecture: Fifty years after Pearl Harbor, 1991 December 3 (Box-folder 70: 26)
  - Chosun Ilbo interview on the 50th anniversary of Pearl Harbor, 1991 December (Box-folder 71: 1)
  - Friday group speech, 1992 February 28 (Box-folder 71: 2)
  - Monthly Chosun interview regarding Kim Dae Jung, 1992 August (Box-folder 71: 3)
  - Notre Dame speech, 1992 November 5 (Box-folder 71: 4)
  - Chosun Ilbo interview, 1992 November 12 (Box-folder 71: 5)
  - Article on Adenauer for Policy Review, 1992 Winter (Box-folder 71: 6)
  - Gopac speech, 1993 January 22 (Box-folder 71: 7)
  - House Republican Conference, 1993 October 20 (Box-folder 71: 8)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference, 1993 November (Box-folder 71: 9)
  - Heritage Foundation Conference on North Korea, 1993 December 15 (Box-folder 71: 10)
  - "Crossfire: Storm clouds over Korea,", 1993 December 28 (Box-folder 71: 11)
  - Introduction of Congressman Hyde at Catholic Campaign, 1994 February 24 (Box-folder 71: 12)
  - Nikkei News article on North Korea, 1994 April-May (Box-folder 71: 13)
  - Asian studies center symposium, 1994 June 21 (Box-folder 71: 14)
  - Speech to the Asian Bankers Association, 1994 November 7 (Box-folder 71: 15)
  - North Korea article in Washington Post, 1994 November 9 (Box-folder 71: 16)
  - North Korea article in Washington Times, 1994 December 27 (Box-folder 71: 17)
  - Taipei American Chamber of Commerce speech, 1995 January 17 (Box-folder 71: 18)
  - SBS interview on U.S.-Korea relations, 1995 January 20 (Box-folder 71: 19)
  - Hanns-Seidel-Stiftung conference in Seoul, 1995 February 28 (Box-folder 71: 20)
  - Remarks on U.S.-North Korea nuclear agreement, 1995 June 15 (Box-folder 71: 21)
  - Metropolitan Club speech, 1995 October 3 (Box-folder 71: 22)
  - Freedom House conference, 1995 October 6 (Box-folder 72: 1)
  - Hanns-Seidel-Stiftung dinner, 1995 November 30 (Box-folder 72: 2)
  - Interview with Lucy Komisar, 1996 July (Box-folder 72: 3)
  - "The Man Who Changed the Game Plan", The National Interest, 1996 Summer (Box-folder 72: 4)
  - Dateline interview regarding Reagan and the Pope against communism, 1996 September 5 (Box-folder 72: 5)
  - Speech at the Institute of Worlds Politics, 1996 October 23 (Box-folder 72: 6)
  - 2nd Anniversary of the U.S.-North Korean nuclear accord remarks, 1996 November 7 (Box-folder 72: 7)
  - "Is America for Sale?" Crossfire, 1997 March 10 (Box-folder 72: 8)
  - Franklin Delano Roosevelt remembrances, 1997 April 15 (Box-folder 72: 9)
  - Interview regarding Kim Dae Jung, 1997 September 30 (Box-folder 72: 10)
  - United States Institute of Peace, 1997 November 14 (Box-folder 72: 11)
  - The U.S. stake in the Korean election, 1997 December (Box-folder 72: 12)
  - Recollections of Ronald Reagan, 1997 (Box-folder 72: 13)
  - On the Korea Tightrope, New York Times, 1998 January 21 (Box-folder 72: 14)
  - Council on Foreign Relations speech on Korea, 1998 January 28 (Box-folder 72: 15)
  - Rheinischer Merkur, 1998 February 12 (Box-folder 72: 16)
  - Korea Club speech, 1998 March 26 (Box-folder 72: 17)
  - Czechoslovakia, 30 Years Ago, Washington Times, 1998 August 21 (Box-folder 72: 18)
  - Festschrift for Jürgen Gebhardt, 1998 August-December (Box-folder 72: 19)
  - Die Welt article on Iraq, 1998 December 21 (Box-folder 72: 20)
  - Ceremony in honor of Franz Josef Strauss, 1998 October 3 (Box-folder 73: 1-2)
  - Franz Josef Strauss Symposium, "Asia's Challenge: The Year 2000 and Beyond,", 1998 November 30 (Box-folder 73: 3)
  - Speech at Council for National Policy conference, 1999 January 22 (Box-folder 73: 4)
  - Reagan legacy celebration, 1999 February 4 (Box-folder 73: 5)
  - Die Welt article on Turkey and Kurds, 1999 February 19 (Box-folder 73: 6)
  - Hoover Symposium remarks on Ronald Reagan, 1999 February 22 (Box-folder 73: 7)
  - "The Cox Committee Report: Shaping the Debate on China," Washington Times, 1999 March 24 (Box-folder 73: 8)
  - NATO conference in Prague speech, 1999 April 23 (Box-folder 73: 9)
  - United States Institute of Peace speech regarding China, 1999 May 14 (Box-folder 73: 10)
  - "Richard Nixon, LBJ, and the Invasion of Czechoslovakia," Hoover Digest, 1999 (Box-folder 73: 11)
- Legal files, 1971-1999 (Box-folder 74-78)
  Contains transcripts of testimony, correspondence, clippings, and notes related to legal cases in which Allen was involved and his testimony before Congress. Of note are materials related to trade, foreign relations, and libel. Arranged in chronological order.
  - Allen vs. Fleming, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 74: 1)
  - Cheatham allegation, 1976 (Box-folder 74: 2-4)
  - Correspondence with Y. Suzuki regarding Cheatham allegation, 1979 (Box-folder 74: 5)
  - Japanese press regarding Cheatham allegation/Grumman, 1979 (Box-folder 74: 6)
  - Department of Justice meeting regarding Nissan, 1979 March (Box-folder 74: 7)
  - Allen vs. Triplett, 1980 (Box-folder 74: 8)
  - Department of Justice reports, 1981 (Box-folder 74: 9)
  - Selected slander articles and DOJ reports, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 74: 10-11)
  - Allen vs. Carmen, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 74: 12-13)
  - Correspondence with Max Mehlman of Arnold and Porter regarding slander, 1983 (Box-folder 75: 1)
  - Testimony to House Committee on Post Office and Civil Service (Debategate), 1984 (Box-folder 75: 2)
  - Slander letter to media, 1984 (Box-folder 75: 3-4)
  - Slander letter to media, master packet, 1984 (Box-folder 75: 5-6)
  - Clippings re: slander and letter to media, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 75: 7)
  - Senate Banking Committee testimony, 1985 September 26 (Box-folder 75: 8)
  - Subcommittee on Asian and Pacific Affairs statement, 1986 April 16 (Box-folder 75: 9)
  - POW/MIA Senate Hearings, 1992 June 23 (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - POW/MIA Senate Hearings: correspondence and backup materials, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 75: 11)
  - POW/MIA Senate Hearings: articles, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 75: 12)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committee testimony on North Korea nuclear agreement, 1995 January (Box-folder 76: 1)
  - Senate Armed Services Committee testimony on North Korea nuclear agreement, 1995 January (Box-folder 76: 2)
  - House Committee on International Relations testimony on South Korea, 1995 March 29 (Box-folder 76: 3)
  - House Committee on Resources testimony on Rails to Trails, 1997 October 30 (Box-folder 76: 4)
  - House Rules Committee testimony regarding China, 1998 June 16 (Box-folder 76: 5)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committee testimony on Taiwan, 1999 August 4 (Box-folder 76: 6)
    Includes list of Allen's testimony before Congress from 1972-1999
  - CLOSED (Box-folder 77)
- Publicity Materials, 1945-1999. (Box-folder 79-93)
  Clippings, press releases, correspondence with journalists, and news wire stories documenting Allen's work, interests, and selected major world events. Includes coverage of foreign policy, national security, trade, prisoners of war, Ronald Reagan, and other political figures. Clippings are also found in significant amounts in the following series: White House files, Campaign files (particularly the Reagan subseries), and Subject files. Arranged in chronological order.
  - St. Francis Preparatory School scrapbook, 1945-1953 (Box-folder 78: 1)
  - Life magazine, 1968 November 15 (Box-folder 89)
  - Nixon-Agnew Elector, 1968 November 2 (Box-folder 89)
  - Nixon resignation newspapers, 1974 August (Box-folder 89)
  - Clippings, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 78: 2)
  - Nixon resignation documents, 1974 August (Box-folder 78: 3)
  - Clippings: 1968 CIA investigation of Allen, 1975 April (Box-folder 78: 4)
  - Death of Mao Tse Tung newspapers, 1976 (Box-folder 90)
  - Carter inauguration newspapers, 1977 (Box-folder 90)
  - Election and Inauguration newspapers, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 90-93)
  - Clippings, 1981 September 1-November 18 (Box-folder 78: 5-12)
  - Clippings, 1981 November 19-December 30 (Box-folder 79: 1-7)
  - Lebanon-Israeli invasion: clippings, briefs, articles, 1982 (Box-folder : 8-9)
  - Clippings, 1982 January (Box-folder : 10-11)
  - Clippings, 1982 April-1984 March (Box-folder 80: 1-10)
  - Clippings, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 81: 1-9)
  - Clippings, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 82: 1-11)
  - Clippings, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 83: 1-11)
  - White House Bulletin, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 84: 1-3)
  - CLOSED (Box-folder 85-88)
- Calendars, 1971-1998 (Box-folder 94-97)
  Appointment books and calendars containing brief descriptions of Allen's schedule. Arranged in chronological order.
  - Appointment books, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 94: 1-3)
  - Appointment books, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 95: 1-4)
  - Appointment book, 1979 (Box-folder 96: 1)
  - Appointment books, 1981, 1987 (Box-folder 2)
  - Appointment books, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 3)
  - Appointment books, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 4-8)
  - Appointment book, 1997 (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - Appointment book and calendar, 1998 (Box-folder : 2)
- Invitations, 1981, 1986 (Box-folder 97-98)
  Consists of invitations to speak, conferences, meetings, and social events.Arranged by type of invitation.
  - Conferences and speaking, 1981 (Box-folder 97: 3-5)
  - Social, 1981 (Box-folder 97: 6-8)
  - Social, 1981 (Box-folder 98: 1-2)
  - White House, 1981 (Box-folder 98: 3-6)
  - Seoul Asian Games, 1986 (Box-folder 98: 7)
- Declassified U.S. government records, 1975-1980
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Includes some records determined by the government to be unclassified; unclassified materials are identified as such in the container list.
  - 2011 June release of records, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 98: 8-11)
    Unclassified records relating to the organization of the National Security Council and the coordination of international economic policy, provided to Allen as background information by Allen J. Lenz, International Trade Administration, U.S. Department of Commerce, in December 1980
- Photographs, 1968-1999 (Box-folder 99-104)
  Includes photographic prints, slides, and negatives documenting Allen's work at the White House, his appearances on the television show Inside Washington, his travels to Asia, speaking engagements, social events, and visits with leaders of other countries, especially Taiwan and South Korea. The series also includes an album documenting the funeral of President Chiang Ching-Kuo of Taiwan. Arranged in chronological order.
  - Allen with others, 66 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 1-5)
  - Visit to Japan, 1 album, undated (Box-folder 99: 6)
  - Richard Armitage, Bruce Willis, Richard Gere, Richard Allen, and others, 2 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 7)
  - Nissan, 1 print, undated (Box-folder 99: 8)
  - Portraits of Allen taken in South Korea, 3 prints and 8 negatives, undated (Box-folder 99: 9)
  - Allen with Helmut Kohl and others, 11 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 10)
  - Allen, taken by Roger Sandler, 3 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 11)
  - Taiwan Ministry of National Defense, 6 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 12)
  - Bishop's visit to the Heritage Foundation, 11 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 13)
  - Trip to South Korea, 7 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 14)
  - Allen with Fukuda Nakajima, 4 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 15)
  - Unidentified party, 7 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 16)
  - Chong Wa Dae, 1 print, undated (Box-folder 99: 17)
  - Inside Washington, 11 prints, undated. (Box-folder 99: 18)
    Includes photographs of television interview of President Gerald Ford
  - Inside Washington, 3 albums, undated. (Box-folder 102)
    Includes photographs of television interview of President Richard Nixon, Stephen Solarz, James Lilley, Jeane Kirkpatrick, John Sununu, Alexander Haig, and Carla Hills
  - Allen during an interview, 8 prints, undated (Box-folder 99: 19)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of Allen with others, 8 prints, circa 1960s (Box-folder 99: 20)
  - Portraits of Richard Allen, 13 prints, 1968 and undated (Box-folder 99: 21)
  - WA photographs, 12 prints, 1969 (Box-folder 99: 22)
    Includes images of US Air Force personnel and aircraft
  - Energy Conferences - Japan, 8 prints, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 99: 23)
  - Asia Oil Company, 4 albums, 1974 (Box-folder 99: 24)
  - Allen and H. C. Yen, 2 prints, 1976 February (Box-folder 99: 25)
  - Tatung Company, 4 prints, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 99: 26)
  - Inauguration, 8 prints, 1977 (Box-folder 99: 27)
  - Chairman M. Toyoda visit, 2 prints, 1978 July (Box-folder 99: 28)
  - White House photographs, 15 prints, circa 1980s (Box-folder 100: 1-2)
  - Walter and Greta, 1 print, 1980 (Box-folder 100: 3)
  - Photographs for Framing, 34 prints, 1980-1999. (Box-folder 100: 4-6)
    Includes list of photographs at Allen's office
  - Party for Jimmy, 1 print, 1981 January (Box-folder 100: 7)
  - Camp David, 5 prints, 1981 June 8 (Box-folder 100: 8)
  - Brady photographs, 2 prints, 31 negatives, 1981 November 9 (Box-folder 100: 9)
  - Allen family at home, 4 contact sheets, 1981 November 30. (Box-folder 100: 10)
    Photographs taken by Terry Arthur for Time
  - Portraits of Allen, 4 contact sheets, 1981 December 6. (Box-folder 100: 11)
    Photographer: Michael Evans
  - Reception for Congressman John LeBoutillier, 6 prints, 1981 December 8 (Box-folder 100: 12)
  - Launch of space shuttle Columbia, 3 prints, 1981 December (Box-folder 100: 13)
  - Friends of Dick Allen luncheon, 16 prints, 1981 December 16 (Box-folder 100: 14)
  - Richard Allen, 3 prints, 1981 (Box-folder 100: 15)
  - NASA onboard photograph of Earth, 1 print, 1981 (Box-folder 100: 16)
  - White House photographs, 40 prints, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 100: 17-19)
  - Unidentified photographs, 13 prints, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 100: 20)
  - Trip to Korea, 12 prints, 1982 September (Box-folder 100: 21)
  - National Security Council staff picnic, 15 prints and 1 35 mm slide, 1982 September 12 (Box-folder 100: 22)
  - Event at Hotel New Otani Tokyo, 6 prints, 1982 December 13 (Box-folder 100: 23)
  - Visits to Taiwan, 21 prints, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 100: 24)
  - John Wei's wedding and baby, 12 prints, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 100: 25)
  - International Democrat Union, 36 prints, 1982-1985. (Box-folder 100: 26-27)
    Includes photographs of George H.W. Bush and Margaret Thatcher
  - Visit to South Korea, 6 prints, 1983 August (Box-folder 100: 28)
  - Allen with Richard von Weizsäcker, 3 prints, 1983 (Box-folder 100: 29)